Jhal
a very good evening friend marriage o'clock jagana
kasana honor drove swift mission possible you have any
person economic experts have mission
impossible life in the service of classes
question of the day shift question aa num
is the question screens
so such question arrangement highway you are you
singing hygiene and on coming Michael is
signaling you suck the couple now you are going to the worry adda khyaati
and you have also used your hands
and the person riding a bike from the front has given
you signal
your bean is what people are going to do so
what will you do drains and beam you will not take Bhim natak uddin because
you feel
unsafe now you will not do it now lobin that you feel
unsafe protest also tubelight that
nikal pass now people will take and whoever is coming from the front will be allowed to go harm to
show your hard splash you will blow the horn to
show that you are feeling comfortable so
come and determine that go inside
You can win one month prizes and
I can answer 10 Glass Talk questions all the best
you have two more to answer this question
and win exciting
prizes we will request you to please share
and ask your family members and friends to
join this campaign and give answers and one in all should
win prizes where is not this
poll campaign is related to road safety
and procedures it is very important and aswar people today
every morning accidents happen and nobody cares
for that there are many
changes on Indian roads and
tried to make a craft requesting you to come
and join this page and this is the
whole work pin is its lesson
and we need your help in making our day fresh you
know that today our front way has
53 from we
give you 5 questions every day in Delhi questions change every 2 hours  You
can participate and you Didi can win more prizes by participating
in five glass questions on this,
we are the question exam highway, you will be on
Amazon coming Michael, this
signal in YouTube and you will not know no no no no no
answer comes, please pick up and
join the video, subscribe to them and
not
request how you think, how can change Shabbir and
training of some things from Tamil, join this
camp in these, these people have understood that now it
means what should you do, everyone knows
what to do but if and
in reality, now this is the opportunity to
write it in your life in reality and bring a change,
if we take small steps
then we will be able to complete this entire Johny
and it cannot be done by one, it is the
responsibility of all of us and we all have to bring this
change together and those in your life,
your love ones, your family members,
your friends, those whom you like,
request them all to be a part
of this campaign and join us
Join this campaign
this evening and change its situation,
we should drown people, follow all the rules and regulations,
this is the emphasis, the answers when one is that
we do it,
our hair comes at 10:00 pm,
drink plants and we drown in it, they
untie, they request you to come and
see your result and chance to
win this prize in GTA and you
can participate in more than one question, you
can win more gifts than this, it was an
attempt of romantic Khar, there is arrangement on my screen,
highway, you are you have been on
coming signal in YouTube and you will not be not been
home to display, this comment,
be a part of this camp, this is a different
start, by being a part of it
and let's make our daily life happy, it has happened, hello hello, it is very important
because
so many accidents happen on daily basis,
so many people leave their homes but never come
back  Or
because of all in excellence and many of these mangoes some people
lose their lives, some get paralyzed,
some become
victims of severe injuries and their life-time
increases in high oil, so by adding that powder
we should change all these things and we should
help them in reducing these drowning injuries because many vehicles are similar, in the
accidents that happen on them,
most of the people who are there are those
who do not wear helmets or they
wear the helmet just for show
or they do not wear it at all, due to which
their
chances increase and the chances of head injury and
sometimes they die due to head injury or they get completely
fried, the helmet
creates a covering, you
use a switch on above your head, you are from a major
health and beauty, so in
this way and how many times it happens
that Om Om has high nose on the highways  But it becomes
very risky and at night
and if we talk about it, a question is
visible here on the highways, so how many
times at night when we are cooking rice,
you will fry me on the
high beam from the front, if you can see a car, that means
someone is coming from the front and it is very simple, then it is
very difficult for the
driver of the car on the opposite side,
because almost the turbulence is concentrated, it becomes
zero, you cannot see what is in
front and what is not, so
now you should always keep this velvet
inside you, your sense should always be in control, thank you, because
you and the lives of other people
also depend on you, if someone is
complying with you, there are other people sitting in the car
or sitting behind you, they are
definitely going at a speed of 250 kmph, that is, the
people who are going on your side, all of us can become
victims of these accidents due to someone's
mistake  So your focus on the road should
always be good. There are
distractions that you should
avoid on the road. Secondly, if
you use your mobile while driving and it is not supported by
that phone, it
means you use it for a long time and their relationship
breaks and they become victims of accidents. So, I am requesting
you to please do not look at it while driving
and people put on screens,
videos are playing in it or something else is going on, then that can
also be a distraction. While driving, I am
requesting you to be a part of this
campaign in Hindi General Knowledge with the Vriddhi
Squares. I also want to talk to you
regarding TV9 Interview Podcast
tv5monde Answers Questions and Win
Exciting Prizes. I am requesting you to join the
campaign with your loved ones like
your family members who are born into
whom you love.  By
making them a part of scrubbing, their
awareness means making the blood more
illegal, regarding ten snakes, a
question is visible on the screen, come quickly
and this is exciting prize of tears,
GTA exam highway, you are coming,
this signaling YouTube alarms in front of you, which are happening
now at night, it
is very dark and you are also using it and the one
coming from in front of you is
giving you a signal that you will
not take a little local, you will
do both of these because you have a partial
person, take it, then Bhim iron, then Bhim
stove curd, tomorrow pass or ask for Bhim, we will do it
and let it go very fast,
you are the splash, now you will go to the horn and will
tell that you are
not feeling well, then you have to answer,
you decide what you will do, in this
way you will come out of this situation
because this time nine driving behave your
self drive while driving Soham
is now connected to us, tell us that  What do you
think about this
relationship? This is the last question of the day. This is
your last chance to
participate for today. This is our
issue. It will run till 18th February. You
can be a part of this campaign.
You have many chances to win more
exciting prizes. We will request you to join this
video. Friends, you and your
family, please answer us. And
now you have the opportunity to learn the option of Merciful Lord. Learn within small
things and steps.
You can learn the scale of driving. If you
go to the job at night and you drink alcohol, then it is
very important for
you to have knowledge of this high sick lobbying. The
screen is half an inch.
Ajay has
Ajay's
show more.
You can check your looks. Our
1052 comes in the App launch speaking and
we can go to the show and
check and check your results and you will be
dead at 10:00 then the last speaking is
inside it or you can go to the website.  You
can reverse our results, turn it on,
a strange attraction now our water,
join us, answers are 18 senior leader Prashant
is Sudhir Dubey Om length otherwise don't get angry,
thank you so much last question answer
and paneer this with us, thank you so much maybe
TV
that a glass question Awadhi video for all,
love you Vinod Jha, love you using AB man
coming difficulties signaling YouTube zoom you will
not over till team not to be because you
feel alarm shuru ho tab Bhim Atulit Vayakalam
pass honge 010 play please MP 10
and stay tuned, thank you so much oo kar
do